http://www.great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
At great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
About Our Cookies
A cookie is a string
of information that great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com stores
on your computer, which your browser provides to great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com
each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and
track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.
Google Analytics Cookies
great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://policies.google.com/privacy. great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on... https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
Advertising Cookies
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. We share this information with these companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.You may opt out of personalized ads for over 125 different ad networks. Click here to do that.Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the Google ad opt-out page.This link from Google provides more information about how Google manages data in its ad products.
Refusing Cookies
You can set your
browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a
cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with
the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for
guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.
If you choose to
refuse great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com's cookies, you may
not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
Personally Identifiable Information
great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com
may collect and use
your personal information for the following purposes:
To
run and operate our site.
To
display content on the site correctly.
To
improve customer service.
To
help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more
efficiently.
To
personalize your user experience.
To
understand how our users as a group use the services and resources
provided on our site.
To
improve our site.
To
improve our products and services.
To
run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.
To
send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think
will be of interest to you.
To
send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or
autoresponder series of emails.
To
respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com
may collect
personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including,
but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out
a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or
resources we make available on our site.Specifically, if you subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for your first name and will require your email address.If you complete a form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for information relevant to the purpose of the form.If you submit content to us, we will ask for your name and email address. Photos you include with your submission, or details in your submission, may personally identify you.If you request to be notified about comments on any content you submit to us, or request to be notified when others submit content, we will require your first name and your email address.If you purchase a product or service from us, we will collect your name, email address, billing address and credit card number. This information may be stored on a third-party's servers.This site lets you share content with your friends and followers on various social media platforms. Below are links to the privacy policies of:FacebookTwiterGoogle +PinterestTumblrRedditgreat-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com also uses Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all of your comments and may show them on your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings.You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.
Non-personally Identifiable Information
We may collect
non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with
our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name,
the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting
to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you
used, and other similar information.
Children's Privacy Protection
This website is
directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We
operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age
of 16 must have a parent or guardian provide consent to use this site. We do
not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone
under 16 years of age.
Release of Information
If we sell great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com,
the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation
in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the
service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice
through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make
reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you
might make.
Data Storage
Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.Some information is collected by third-party services. These include PayPal.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to download and review that information, click on this link. You can also request to edit, download or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on this link.
Updates and Effective Date
great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com
reserves the right to
make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and
privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have
changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to
periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we
collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree
to great-pyrenees-club-of-southern-ontario.com's privacy policy as
posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies
and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent
indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.
Last updated: August 5, 2018
There are many dogs in need. Please help us reduce their misery. Save a Great Pyr.
CLICK to Donate
HomeLatest Site AdditionsABOUT OUR CLUBExecutive WelcomeJoin The ClubMembership RenewalClub EventsIn Memory of SandraPrivate Rescue OnlyABOUT OUR DOGSDogs of the ClubGreat Pyr IntroductionThe Breed StandardGreat Pyr BehaviourPyr TemperamentGreat Pyr GuardianshipDogs and ChildrenWorking Great PyrsWorking Pyrs Part 2Take The Pyr ExamSERVICES FOR YOUContact UsGreat Pyr RescueFoster a PyrPet ID FundraiserHappy TailsRainbow BridgeAbout BreedersPuppies AvailableShare Your Pyr StoriesGreat Pyr QuestionsResourcesSanta BuddiesAbout This SitePrivacy Policy
[?]Subscribe To This Site
CLICK TO FOSTER A PYR
PLEASE CLICK THE IMAGE
Breaking News
Shaven Pyr Dec 10, 20 03:30 PMShe has always been energetic, but when she got home from grooming(we got her shaved to her undercoat, sorry) she was usually calm. I'm used to her running Read More
Neutering Dec 02, 20 02:12 PMIs it safe to neuter a 5-year old male? I see different answers everywhere. Thank you Read More
Darby Dec 02, 20 09:52 AM*ADOPTION PENDING*
Darby, a year-old Maremma, came to us with some fear issues. Anne, our trainer, assessed him to be fearful of other dogs but with work Read More
Protective Nov 19, 20 07:00 AMI have a 5-month-old Mel great Pyrenees named Koda. We've had him since he was 12 weeks old and are absolutely amazed by how quickly he was able to work Read More
Darby Nov 18, 20 02:29 PMThis beautiful young year-old Maremma needs to have his confidence built up. We are working on this and is to be continued by his new people.
He is fearful Read More
Sunny Nov 18, 20 02:26 PM *ADOPTION PENDING*
This young white fluffy mix is a sweet girl who is typical of her primary breed. She gets along with other dogs with proper introduction. Read More
Dewclaws - Single and Double Nov 18, 20 12:08 PMI got three pups from a breeder and 2 of the pups have double dew claws in the back but the 1 only has single dewclaw in the back how is this possible Read More
Oliver Nov 09, 20 12:45 PMCongratulations to Oliver and his family. He has been officially adopted!
DOB: March 30, 2019
This big white fluffy––Maremma maybe Retriever cross––came Read More
© All rights reserved. All content copyright protected 2005 - 2020
Reproduction by any means is prohibited without specific written permission
SBI!
